there's been public reporting that Jeffrey Epstein showed people photos of
President Trump with half-naked young women. Do you know if the FBI found those
photographs in their search of Jeffrey Epstein's safe or premises or otherwise?
Have you seen any such thing?
You know, Senator Whitehouse, you sit here and make
salacious remarks once again trying to slander President Trump left and right
when you're the one who was taking money from one of Epstein's closest
confidants, I believe, I could be wrong, correct me, Reid Hoffman, who was with
Jeffrey Epstein on multiple occasions and the senator sitting right next to
you tried to block the flight logs from being released, yet you're grilling me on
President Trump and some photograph with Epstein? Come on.
The question is...